<?xml version="1.0"?>
<sr-row>
    <row>
        <title>International Courier</title>
        <p>At CourierTrust, we offer international courier
            services to our clients who need to send their packages to any part of the world. We
            understand the importance of timely delivery, and that's why we strive to provide efficient
            and reliable services. With our network of trusted partners and years of experience in the
            industry, we can deliver your package safely and on time.</p>
        <p2>Our international courier services cover a wide range of packages, including documents,
            parcels, and cargo. We use the latest technology to track your package in real-time,
            ensuring that you are aware of its location throughout its journey. We also provide customs
            clearance assistance, making the process easier for you and ensuring that your package
            arrives at its destination without any delays or additional charges.</p2>
        <p3> At CourierTrust, we understand that every package is unique and may require special
            handling or packaging. That's why we offer customized solutions to meet your specific needs,
            including express delivery, door-to-door delivery, and packaging services. </p3>
        <price>2000/kgRs.</price>s <img>./images/card-1-photo.jpg</img>
    </row>

    <row>
        <title>Truckload courier</title>
        <p>Our truckload courier service is the perfect solution for customers who need to
            transport large amounts of goods or materials across long distances. With our modern
            fleet of trucks and experienced drivers, we can ensure that your cargo will arrive
            safely and on time. We offer flexible scheduling options and competitive pricing to meet
            your needs and budget.</p>
        <p2>Our team of professionals will work closely with you to determine the best routing and
            delivery options for your shipment. We understand that every customer has unique
            requirements and we strive to tailor our services to meet those needs. We also provide
            real-time tracking of your shipment so that you can stay informed about its location and
            delivery status.</p2>
        <p3> At CourierTrust, we pride ourselves on providing exceptional customer service and
            support. Our friendly and knowledgeable staff is available to answer your questions and
            provide assistance throughout the entire shipping process. we are committed to
            delivering the highest level of service and reliability to our customers.</p3>
        <price>1000/kg Rs.</price>
        <img>./images/card-2-img.jpg</img>
    </row>

    <row>
        <title>Normal Courier</title>
        <p>Normal courier is a reliable and cost-effective option for sending documents and small
            packages within a city or across the country. With our Normal courier service, you can
            enjoy a hassle-free delivery experience, as we handle everything from pick-up to
            delivery.</p>
        <p2>Our Normal courier service is perfect for individuals and businesses who need to send
            important documents or small items, such as contracts, agreements, letters, or samples.
            We understand the importance of time-sensitive deliveries, which is why we always
            prioritize timely delivery and provide real-time tracking information to our customers.</p2>
        <p3>At courierTrust, we pride ourselves on our commitment to providing excellent customer
            service, and our Normal courier service is no exception. Our team of experienced
            professionals ensures that every delivery is handled with care and attention to detail,
            so you can have peace of mind knowing that your package is in good hands. Trust us to
            deliver your packages on time and with the utmost care!</p3>
        <price>200/kg Rs.</price>
        <button></button>
        <img>./images/card-3-img.jpg</img>
    </row>
</sr-row>